infonow.com 2013-08-22

# Channelinsight Privacy Policy | Our Commitment to Online Privacy

## Our Commitment to Online Privacy

Channelinsight is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website. To accomplish this, we have implemented this Online Privacy Policy that governs all information collected on or submitted to our website. To make this Online Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage. By accessing, browsing or using the Site, you acknowledge that you read, understand, and agree to the terms and conditions of Channelinsight's Online Privacy Policy. **Please review this Online Privacy Policy each time you visit this Site to understand any changes that we may have made to the Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not access, browse, or use this Site.**

### What Information We Collect on our Site and How We Use It

1. Non-Personal and Aggregated Information Collected Automatically.
    When you visit our Site, we log general data, such as your domain name, name of the Web page from which you entered our Site, which pages you visit on our Site, and how much time you spend on each page. We use this information to continually monitor and improve our Site and for internal analysis. In particular, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather information for aggregate use.
2. Personal Information That You Choose to Submit.
    As a visitor to our Site, you may choose to use the Site to send us personal information (e.g., your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address), for example, when you send a question via the Site, register for a special service, submit your resume through our Site. Anytime you submit personal information for a specific purpose using the Site, your information is used for that purpose only, unless you consent otherwise or as required by law.

We do not send unsolicited e-mail to you or other visitors to our Site. We may use e-mail to respond to e-mail messages from you, where necessary, to confirm information received online from you and to engage in other communication that you have authorized or that we have determined necessary to more effectively service you.

In many cases, you choose the amount of information you supply (e.g., when sending us information through the Site, you may choose to include only an e-mail address - not a telephone number or mailing address - for replies).

### "What About "Cookies"?

The term "cookie" refers to files that are transferred from a website to your computer's hard drive. The purpose of cookies is to enable us to track your activities on our Site. Cookies help us remember who you are. They work in the same fashion as the clerk in a store you visit on a regular basis. The store clerk may not necessarily know your name, but he or she recognizes that you have been in the store before and may remember what you usually purchase while you are in the store. Cookies permit us to gain the same kind of information about you and enable us to provide you with more efficient and personalized service. For example, for sites that require registration, a cookie file can be stored on your computer enabling you to skip the registration process on subsequent visits. Cookies are also frequently used to track the progression of a customer engaged in an online purchase to ensure that the transactional information remains intact.

Some (usually newer) versions of Web browsers allow you to decide whether or not to accept cookie files and some programs notify you when a website is about to deposit a cookie file on your hard drive. If you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to successfully navigate some portions of a website.

InfoNow uses cookie files for the customized presentation of Web pages. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in the cookie, nor do we use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, except as expressly set forth in this Policy.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through the Site. However, please be advised that InfoNow cannot guarantee and has no control over the public or third party network through which you send your personal information.

### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

We do not collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Site is intended for anyone under 13 years of age. By entering this Site, users represent that they are 13 years of age or older.

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact us.
